Title, The Last Message.
Alina still texted Leo every morning, even though he hadn't answered in weeks.
It had started as a habit, asterisk, good morning, love, asterisk, but now it was more
like a prayer.
She knew something was wrong, no one just disappears, not someone like Leo.
They had loved fiercely, not the gentle, sitcom kind of love, no theirs had been wild, alive.
They met in college, fought the world together, shared dreams, built a small life in a tiny
apartment filled with plants and laughter and vinyl records.
Then Leo got the call for a journalism assignment in a conflict zone.
He promised it was only for two weeks.
He left her with a kiss and the same line he always said, I'll write you every day,
no matter what.
And he did, until day 11.
The silence was unbearable.
Alina called the agency, no news.
She contacted embassies, friends, strangers, weeks passed.
Her texts turned from cheerful to desperate.
Then one evening, a man knocked at her door.
His uniform said everything, his eyes even more.
Leo had been taken by a militia group.
They tortured him for information.
When they found his notebook, filled with names, photos, stories, they deemed him a
spy.
They made a video, they made her watch.
The camera didn't flinch, but she did.
She screamed.
He cried until no sound came out.
They mailed her his watch, that stupid watch with the cracked face he refused to replace.
It still ticked.
Alina didn't speak much after that.
She still texted him every morning.
Until one day, she left her phone beside the watch on the table and walked into the ocean.
No goodbyes.
Just a message on the lock screen.
I miss you, even where there are no words left.